City of Newburgh Urban Renewal; Collection apap375
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administrative, 1945-2000; 1
  - Reading File, June 1973 (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - Reading File, July 1973 (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - Reading File, August 1973 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Reading File, September 1973 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Reading File, October 1973 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Reading File, November 1973 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Reading File, December 1973 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Reading File, January 1974 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Reading File, February 1974 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Reading File, March 1974 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Reading File, April 1974 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Reading File, May 1974 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Reading File, June 1974 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Reading File, July 1974 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Reading File, August 1974 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Reading File, September 1974 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Reading File, October 1974 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Reading File, November 1974 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Reading File, December 1974 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Reading File January 1975 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Reading File February 1975 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Reading File March 1975 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Reading File April 1975 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Reading File May 1975 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Reading File June 1975 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Reading File July 1975 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Reading File August 1975 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Reading File September 1975 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Reading File October 1975 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Reading File November 1975 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Reading File December 1975 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Reading File January 1976 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Reading File February 1976 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Reading File March 1976 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Reading File April 1976 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Reading File May 1976 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Reading File June 1976 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Reading File July 1976 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Reading File August 1976 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Reading File September 1976 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Reading File October 1976 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Reading File November 1976 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Reading File December 1976 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Reading File, 1976-1977; 1979 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Reading File January 1977 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Reading File February 1977 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Reading File March 1977 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Reading File April 1977 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Reading File May 1977 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Reading File June 1977 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Reading File July 1977 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Reading File August 1977 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Reading File September 1977 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Ready to Type Deeds, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate Developer Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Real Estate Lists, 1961 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Revolving Fund and Cash Disbursement Rev. Fund, 1966-1976 (Item 6)
  - Redevelopers Statements, 1961 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Redevelopers Summary, 1958 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Reg-100, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Rehab File, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Rehab of Washington Terrace Little Britain Road, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Rehabilitating Historic Buildings Information, 1982-1983; Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Rehabilitation and Conservation Report, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Rehabilitation and Financing Handbook HUD, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Rehabilitation Applicants, 1975-1979; 1985-1988 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Rehabilitation Projects, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Release to Press, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Relocation Progress Reports, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Relocation Survey Pilot Report March 1967 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Renovation and Rehabilitation Bourne Apartments NYS 60A, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Rent 83.3E, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Rental Rehabilitation Technical Info, 1982; Undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Rentals, 1983-1984 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Report Forms, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Report on Urban Renewal Plan and Planning, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Report Summary Sheets: Statistics Pertaining to Acquisition, 1970-1971 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Report Upon Examination of Financial Statements and Supplemental Data, 1972-1975 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Request for Consent to Transfer Funds NYA-10, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Request for HUD Concurrence Acquisition Prices NDP, 1971-1973 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Residential and Nonresidential Structure Surveys, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Resolutions, 1966-1967 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Resolutions, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Resolutions, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Resolutions cont'd, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Resolutions, 1984-1985 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Resolutions City Council Discontinuing Streets Etc., 1973 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Resolutions for 1971 and 1972, 1971-1972; 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Returned Check Slips, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Reuse Appraisal, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Reuse Appraisal 1973 Pomerantz NYR189 14 Parcels, 1973-1974 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Rev. Lucas First Born Church of the Living God, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Revised Computations, 1984; Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Revolving Fund, 1967-1976 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Richard Venuti, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 83)
  - Rights of Entry NYR 189, 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Ritangela Constr. Corp NYA-10, 1971; 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Ritangela Construction Corp, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 82)
  - Ritangela Construction Corp, 1972-1975 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Robert Davis Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1962-1965 (Box 64, Folder 30)
  - Robinson, Landers, Chamber Street, 1984-1986 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Rockwell Vending, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Roger Schafer, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Roger Schafer, 1967-1968; Undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Ronald Santa, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Rosen, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Rosenblum Architects, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Rough Grading and Site Clearance, NYA-10, NYR-189, 1975; Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Ruby Reid Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1962-1966 (Box 64, Folder 60)
  - Rural Delivery An Affordable Alternative, 1993-1994 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Rusciano Appraisers, 1970-1973 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Rusciano Appraisers, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Rusciano Documents Lake Street, 1970-1972 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - S. Parr Pedestrian Bridge, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Saffioti Condemnation Lawsuit, 1981-1982 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Salaries 83.1E, 1983-1984 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Sale of Land to UDC, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Sales Book, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Sam Rubinberg- Hardware, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Samuel Berkowsky, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Samuel Z Mandel, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Sanitary Science and Laboratories, Inc., 1973 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - SAS Equipment Co, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Schultz Builders, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Schwaner, Justus, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Scott Woodhull, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - SDA Tabernacle Church, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Second Amendatory Contract, NYS Capital Grant, NDP Project NYA-10, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Second Bids received for 97 Grand St., 1980 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Secondino Risio, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Section 312 Rehabilitation Loan Program, 1980-1981 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Selling of City Owned Buildings, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Seward and Kissel Draft, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Sewer Re-Connection, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Shapiro, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Sharpe, Gilbert, 122 Montgomery Street, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Sharpes Barber Shop 169 Water Street, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Sherrill and Arnold Mitton, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Shiffman, 1970-1972 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Shop Drawings Washington Terrace, 1989; Undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Shorthand Notes Green and White Spiral Notebook, 1967; Undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Sidney Pollack, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Silver Front Bar and Grill, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Site Preparation and Project Improvements, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Site Work and Rehabilitations, 1984; 1989 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Sketches and Maps, Undated (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Slater Williams, 1972; 1976 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Small Business Administration Notices, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - Small Cities Assessment Reports, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Smiths TV Store, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Soil Testing Inc, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Solomon Ware, Ware's Clothing Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Sonny's Snack Bar, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Sonyma, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - South Miller Street Homeownership Program Master Specs. 1, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - South Miller Street Homeownership Program Master Specs. 2, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Specifications for 11 Hudson View Terrace, 51 Carson Ave, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Specifications for 3 Johnes Street, 667 South Street, 6 Forsythe Place, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Specifications for 94 Benkard Ave. Gerald and Barbara Richardson, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Specifications for 95 Dubois Street, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Specifications for Demolition #10, 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Specifications for Demolition #9, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Specifications for Demolition Contract No. 3-189, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Specifications for Lower Broadway Facade Easement, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Specifications for Lower Broadway Facade Easement, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Specifications for Rehabilitation by Robert Nilsson and Associates (Red), 1984 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Specifications for Rehabilitation of 258 Montgomery, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Specifications for the Rehabilitation of 16 Farrington Street, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Specifications for the Rehabilitation of 281 Grand Street, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Specifications for the Rehabilitation of 79 Lander Street, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Specifications for the Rental Rehabilitation of 202 South Street, Undated (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Specifications, Payments, Correspondence, Insurance, 1972; Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Specified Work List and Rehab Standards, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Specified Work List and Rehabilitation Standards 188 Liberty Street, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Specs for Weather Proofing Contract #1, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Specs for Weather Proofing Contract #2, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - State Contract Application NYA-10 Second Year, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - State Urban Renewal Fund, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Stein and Zaransky, 1971-1975 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Steno's Bills, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Stepski, 1967-1969 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Stepski Minutes Original, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Street Reconstruction and Re-Alignment, NYR-189, High St., Montgomery St., 1975; Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Structural Review: 135 Lander Street, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Struthers, Cathy 165 Water Street, 1965 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Sunday Record Profile Addition, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Supporting Data in Connection with Allocation of Rental Units, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Survey Descriptions, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Survey Descriptions, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Susan Sorrentino, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Sylcox 237 Montgomery, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Tabulation of Areas of Land Disposition, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Tax Info, 1984-1986; 1988-1990 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Tax Map Properties Identified as City of Newburgh Property, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Tax Receipts, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Tax Sale Certificate Cancellations, 1970-1973 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Technical Specifications, 1982-1983 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Teen Information Peer Services, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Temes, Esq. Contract Work, 1968; 1970-1972 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Tenant Ledgers, 1962 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Terry Cheatom Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Terry Cheatom, North End Rest, 1962; 1965 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Thelma Davis Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1963-1966 (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - Thelma Lewis Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1962-1964 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Theodore Conrad, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - Theresa Hayden and M DeVito 5-9 Wash Terr, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Thomas Herbert, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Thomas W Chadwick, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Time Sheets Summer (1 of 2), 1970 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Time Sheets Summer (2 of 2), 1970 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Time Sheets February through March 1971 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Time Sheets April through June 1971 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Time Sheets July through September 1971 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Time Sheets December 1971 and August 1972, 1971-1972 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Time Sheets 1972 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Title Company Correspondence, 1961-1968 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Title Reports, 189, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Title Reports, NYR 189, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - To Bard Chevrolet Inc, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Toback, 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Tom Reidy Landlord Inner-city Rehab Co., 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Traffic Control, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Transient Housing Facilities, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Travel 83.6E, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Travers and Madoff, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Trial Balances and Grant Applications, 1972-1975 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Troy Smith Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1961; 1965-1966 (Box 64, Folder 51)
  - U.R. 59 Chambers Street and 61 Chambers Street, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - UDC Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - UDC Redevelopers Statement for Public Disclosure, 1969-1971 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Ulrich Asmann, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Up to 1970, 1969-1970; Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Updating Lake Street Project Parcels Nos 6,7,8A,10, 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - UR 4-1-1 Map Attached in Back, 1961 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - UR Amendment 1992 Stuart Turner Updated Agreement (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - UR Consultants, 1958 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - UR Demolition Contract #3 June 1970 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Urban Development 1965, 1965-1967; 1976-1978 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Urban Development Corp, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Urban Ren. Contractors Ledger (Green), 1971-1973 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Urban Renewal Business and Industrial Development Director Carnes, 1976-1977 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Urban Renewal circa 1986-1988 Green Ledger (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Urban Renewal Demolition Contract No. 10 City of Newburgh, NY, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Urban Renewal Demolition Funds, cost. Etc., 1969-1970 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Urban Renewal Disposition Parcel Maps, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Urban Renewal Handbook, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Urban Renewal Individual Property Assessments for State Housing, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Urban Renewal Investment Book, 1971-1975 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Urban Renewal Ledger: General, Expense, Feasibility Study, 1961-1969 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Urban Renewal Master Plan- Public Hearing Comments, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Urban Renewal Payroll Records NYA-10-RESTRICTED, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Urban Renewal Personnel Charges Demolition, 1962-1963; 1974 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Urban Renewal Plan Accepted, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Urban Renewal Project NYR 189 Demolition Contract No. 13-189, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Urban Renewal Risio, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Urban Renewal Rosen Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Urban Renewal South West Street Park- Schlermacher Park, 1971-1973 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Urban Renewal Studies and Papers, 1964; 1995 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Urban Renewal Wilson, 1970-1972 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Urban Renewal: Interstate Industrial 1960s Storeroom and Raw Mat., 1967; Undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Urban Renewal: Preservation, Correspondence, City Historian, 1962-1964; 1967-1970 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Urban Shopsteading Agreement, 1982-1983 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Urban Shopsteading FY 84, 1983-1986 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Urban Shopsteading Program, 1982-1983 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Utilities 83.4E, 1983-1985 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Vacate Notices NYR 189, 1970-1973 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Valente and Sullivan, Inc, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Vandervoort, Clara, 303 Water Street, 1965 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Van's Market, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Varick Homes Housing Develop. Fund Co. HUD Form 6004, 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Vauck Homes, 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Vauck Homes, cont'd, 1965-1970 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Vaughn, Emily, 257 Water Street, 1964 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Vehicle Expenses 83.8E, 1983-1984 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Vermont Terminal Corp, 1972-1973 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Vermont Terminal Corp End of West Street Parcel 30, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Victors Market, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Volume No. 1 Newburgh Urban Renewal Agency Minutes of Mtgs., 1965-1967 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Vouchers Bureau of Audit and Control, 1983-1984 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Vouchers for Travel, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 75)
  - Vouchers- Maintenance and Boarding Up, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Vouchers- Temporary Relocation, 1961-1962 (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - W.E. Atkins Lodge, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Walker, Ben 312 Water Street, 1965-1966 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Ware's Used Clothing, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Warren S Craig, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Wash. Ter., 1973-1974; Undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Washington Terrace, Highland Provision Company, 1971-1972 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Water Department, 1971-1973 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Water Meter Removals, 1969-1970 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Water Street Barbeque Rest, 1961; 1963; 1966 (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Waterside Place, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Waterside Place Corporation Disposition Parcel #34, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Watson Exhibits, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Watson Hearings, 1966-1968 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Watson Motions and Orders, 1967-1968 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Watson Report, 1967-1968 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Watson's Liquor Store, 1961; 1963; 1965-1968 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Webco Processing Co. Inc., 1972 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Webco Processing Company, 1971-1972 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - West Industry Street Design and Resident Supervision, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - West Street Park, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Weyant Smith 116 Prospect Street, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Wilbert Boykin Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1965-1966 (Box 64, Folder 35)
  - Wilbur Boykin 238 Water Street, 1963 (Box 64, Folder 39)
  - William Elferis, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - William J Dillon, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - William McMillan, Gee's Awning Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - William Silverstein, 134-136 Water Street, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - William Silverstein, 147 Water Street, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Williams, 75 Third St., 1972 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Williams, Grace 257 Water Street, 1963-1964 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Willie Burks Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1963-1966 (Box 64, Folder 36)
  - Windsor Building Supplies Company, Inc., 1973; 1976 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Winstead, Dorothy, 169 Water Street, 1961-1964 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Winterization of the Glen Hines Memorial Center 285 Liberty Street, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - WM J. Lamont, 1961-1962 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Woodward Construction Inc, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Workable Program Completed Report, 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Workday Descriptions, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Workman's Comp: Primous Harris 1967 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - YMCA, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - YMCA Camp Scholarship Program, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - YMCA Rehabilitation, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Zanzi, 82 Smith Street, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Zeckendorf Form 6004, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 10)